National Negro Opera Company Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1934-1970, (193 folders) (Box 7-12)
  - Form letters. Correspondence to Parents of the NNOC Foundation, Inc. Youth Guild, 1953 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Envelopes. Addressed but not postmarked, 1949 and undated (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Envelopes. Postmarked, but not further identified, 1938, 1944, 1947-1948, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - NNOC stationary, undated (Box-folder 12/31)
- Photographs, 1925-1994, (206 folders) (Box 13-16, 65-67)
  Identified and unidentified photographic images of individuals and groups related to the National Negro Opera Company, its member guilds, committees and other affiliated African American groups and organizations. As many of the photographs in this collection were used for various programs and publicity purposes, several images will be found cut to the needs of the National Negro Opera Company. Some post-1962 photographs document various honors awarded to Mary Cardwell Dawson after her death.
  Identified photographs arranged alphabetically by name.
  - Identified Individuals, Groups and Productions (Box 13-16, 65-67)
    - Achille, Marcel, 1961, Biographical information typed on back of photograph. (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Aida, undated (Box-folder 13/2, 65/9)
      17 photographs (several taken from publications).
    - Alexander, Robert, undated (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Anderson, Marian, February 19, 1961 and undated, Ten photographs taken at a reception for Marian Anderson, Chicago, Palmer House, Feb. 19, 1961; also - three portrait photographs (one is autographed) (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Anglin, John, undated (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Avalone, Blanche, undated, Surname also spelled Avaloni in a few programs. (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Beasley, Moses, 1947, Two different photographs of Rev. Beasley, one dated April 28, 1947. (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Beckom, O'Labrice, undated (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Bell, Ivy Ponyat, undated (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Bell, Teresa (McDaniel), undated (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Bivens, James R., March 1934 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Bost, Fran, 1944 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Boyd, Gordon, undated, [Fragile] (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Bragg, Bertha, undated, Two different photographs. (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Bragg, Edward, undated (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Brice, Carol, undated, Five photographs with one image being with her brother - Jonathan Brice. (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Brown, Debria, December 15 and 26, 1958 and undated, Five photographs: Four different photographs (Carl Van Vechten, photographer) as Carmen, dated December 1958; one image from Aida (undated) (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Brown, Gertrude, undated (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Cardwell, James A., undated, James A. Cardwell was the father of Mary Cardwell Dawson.; Two different photographs. (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Cardwell Dawson Choir, 1938 and undated, Eight photographs.; One photograph is a inscribed formal portrait of the Cardwell Dawson Choir (Mary Cardwell Dawson's pupils), dated 1938, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Cardwell School of Music. Commemorative [Historical marker] dedication, September 25, 1994 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Carrington, Rita Maria, undated (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Cato, Minto, undated, Seven photographs. (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Causey, Willa, undated (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Choruses, 1938 and undated, 12 photographs (formal portraits, informal images and others taken from live performances) (Box-folder 13/25, 66/2)
    - Choruses (Washington. D.C. Opera Guild Chorus), undated, 2 photographs (formal portrait of the entire opera chorus) (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Coleman, Charles (?), 1943, As Elder Germont in La Traviata, Civic Opera House, Chicago. (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Copland, Gloria, undated, Added notation: Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Crawford, Alice, undated (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Crawford, Alice Davis, undated (Box-folder 13/29)
    - Dance group (non-production), undated (Box-folder 13/30)
    - Dawson, Mary Cardwell - alone, undated, 19 photographs. (Box-folder 13/31, 65/1, 66/1)
    - Dawson, Mary Cardwell - with others, June 24, 1927, 1941 and undated, 14 photographs.; Includes several photographs of Mary and Walter M. Dawson, including a large wedding day image, dated June 24, 1927.; Other images of Mary Cardwell Dawson can be found throughout the photographic collections that contain group images of the various NNOC/NNOF Guilds, committees, rehearsals, concerts and publicity. (Box-folder 13/32)
    - Dawson, Walter M., 1925 and undated, Seven photographs, including three different portrait images, one group photograph (Wentworth Institute, Boston, MA where he majored in electrical engineering, graduating in June 1925) and three candid images of Mr. Dawson operating machinery at work.; Other images of Walter M. Dawson can be found throughout the various group photographs of various NNOC/NNOF Guilds and committees. (Box-folder 13/33)
    - Dett, Helen (Mrs. R. Nathaniel Dett), undated (Box-folder 13/34)
    - Duncan, Todd, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/35)
    - Duncan, Vernon, undated, Photograph is notated as "Haitian Voodoo ceremony." (Box-folder 13/36)
    - Early, Johnny, undated, Also included: a one-page biographical summary. (Box-folder 13/37)
    - Elzy, Ruby, 1942, Photograph is inscribed to Mrs. Dawson from Ms. Elzy. (Box-folder 13/38)
    - Evanti, Lillian, undated, Three photographs (two inscribed photographs). (Box-folder 13/39)
    - Faust, undated (Box-folder 13/40)
      Seven photographs: One photograph from a live performance and six photographic images from illustrations taken from the opera.
    - Flying Clouds Progressive IV (vocal group), undated (Box-folder 13/41)
    - "Footprints on the sands of time," in honor of Madam Mary Cardwell Dawson and Horace Wilson, April 28, 1963 (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Fountain, Beatrice, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/43)
    - Franchois, Priscilla Mays, undated (Box-folder 13/44)
    - Franklin, Walter, undated (Box-folder 13/45)
    - Franklin, William, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 13/46)
    - Fulbright, James William (Senator: Arkansas), undated, Photograph of Senator Fulbright with Mary Cardwell Dawson. (Box-folder 13/47)
    - Gardner, Katherine Cardwell, undated (Box-folder 13/48)
    - Gatto, Angelo, undated, Four photographs. (Box-folder 13/49)
    - Glass, Hazel - James L. Cornitcher wedding photograph, undated (Box-folder 13/50)
    - Graham, Michael Angelo, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 13/51)
    - Graham, Walter, undated, Walter Graham was Music Director, Chicago Music Conservatory. (Box-folder 13/52)
    - Grant, Albert J., undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/53)
    - Greene, Evelyn, undated (Box-folder 13/54)
    - Greenidge, Lisle, undated (Box-folder 13/55)
    - Gwin, Huel Brooks, undated (Box-folder 13/56)
    - Haley, Si Lita (Mrs. Frederick Vajda), undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/57)
    - Hamilton, Gwendolyn, undated (Box-folder 13/58)
    - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), August 30, 1934 and undated, Six photographs.; One photograph is inscribed to Walter Dawson, August 30, 1934. (Box-folder 13/59)
    - Harris, Ethel Ramos, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/60)
    - Harrison, Hazel, undated (Box-folder 13/61)
    - Harrison, Pearlie Cox, undated (Box-folder 13/62)
    - Hatchett, Starling, undated (Box-folder 13/63)
    - Henderson, George, undated (Box-folder 13/64)
    - Henderson, Luther, undated (Box-folder 13/65)
    - Herbert, Ralph, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 13/66)
    - Hightower, Madeline undated (Box-folder 13/67)
    - Hill, Bernice, undated (Box-folder 13/68)
    - Hinderas, Natalie, undated, Six photographs. (Box-folder 13/69)
    - Holmes, Dorothy, 1947 (Box-folder 13/70)
    - Holland-Forbes, Kathleen, undated, Water-related damage. (Box-folder 13/71)
    - Holt, Nora, undated (Box-folder 13/72)
    - Honory, Marvin, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 13/73)
    - Hood, Priscilla, undated (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Hudgins, William R., undated (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Insana, Silvio, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Interdenominational Ushers Union (Church ushers organization), undated, Walter M. Dawson was active in this organization.; Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Johnson, Gertrude (Bell), undated see also Correspondence: Bell, Gertrude Johnson, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Johnson, Jeanne, undated, Inscribed photograph. (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Jones, Cynthia, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Kelly, John P., undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Keyes, Pansy, undated (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Kimbrough, A. L., undated (Box-folder 14/10)
    - King, Janice, undated (Box-folder 14/11)
    - King, Juanita, undated, Seven photographs. (Box-folder 14/12)
    - King, Omega, undated (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Knox, Ethel C., undated (Box-folder 14/14)
    - La Tour, Lou, undated (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Lee, Barbara Edwards, undated (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Lee, Grace, undated (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Leer, David and Mary Beckett, undated (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Leer, David and Mary Veaney (Rash), undated (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Leer, David with Mary Beckett and Mary Veaney (Rash), undated (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Lehmann, Otto, circa 1944 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Lewis, Bernice Hammond, April 30, 1949 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Lipscomb, Joseph, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Lucas, James, undated (Box-folder 14/23)
    - McAllister, Hazel, undated (Box-folder 14/24)
    - McBrown, Gertrude, undated (Box-folder 14/25)
    - McCleave, Florence Cole, undated (Box-folder 14/26)
    - McFerrin, Robert, undated (Box-folder 14/27)
    - McKenzie, Donald L., undated, Photograph is inscribed to Mme. Dawson. (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Marshall, Adrienne, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Maynor, Dorothy, 1940, Inscribed to Mary Cardwell Dawson. (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Metropolitan A.M.E. Church. Group (Washington, D.C.), undated (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Miles, Betty Mansfield, undated (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Millander, "Lucky", undated, Four photographs. (Box-folder 14/33)
    - Miss Metropolitan (Washington, D.C.) Crown Competition (queen competition), 1953, Four photographs. (Box-folder 14/34)
    - Montgomery, Alma (piano accompanist), undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/35)
    - Montgomery, Alma (soprano), undated, Different individual from previous folder. (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Morris, Ben Mitchell, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Murphy, Pearl, undated (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Music Festivals, Griffith Stadium, Washington, D.C., 1947-1955, 73 photographs, taken during the nine annual festivals presented at Griffith Stadium. (Box-folder 14/39, 65/9)
    - National Association of Negro Musicians (NANM), circa 1950s (Box-folder 14/40)
    - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc. 18th Annual Convention, St. Louis, MO., August 20-27, 1937, Camille L. Nickerson, President.; Oversize photo. (Box-folder 16/1)
    - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc. 19th Annual Convention, Kansas City, Kansas, August 21-26, 1938, Kemper Harris, President; J. Roy Terry, Vice-President.; Oversize photo. (Box-folder 67/1)
    - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc. 20th Annual Convention, Chicago, Ill., August 18-23, 1940, Mary Cardwell Dawson, President.; Oversize photo. (Box-folder 67/1)
    - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc. Convention, Pittsburgh, PA, August 24-29, 1941, Mary Cardwell Dawson, President.; Oversize photo. (Box-folder 16/2)
    - National Negro Opera Company Foundation, 1950 and undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/41)
    - National Negro Opera Company Foundation. Youth Guild, 1953 and undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Neal, Mansfield, circa 1944, Three photographs. (Box-folder 14/43, 65/2)
    - Nespoli, Uriel, undated, Five photographs. (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Nichols, Shelby, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/45)
    - Nyoka, Princess Consuelo, undated, Two photographs.; One photograph is fragile (torn in two pieces) (Box-folder 14/46)
    - Offord, J., undated (Box-folder 14/47)
    - Olsen, Robert, undated (Box-folder 14/48)
    - The Ordering of Moses, July 28, 1950 and undated, 17 photographs; one additional sheet contains eight small photographic copies.; Several photographs are from the performance of July 28, 1950, Washington, D.C., Griffith Stadium. (Box-folder 14/49, 65/10)
    - Ouanga, circa 1956, Seven photographs (one photograph is a non-performance image that includes Clarence White and Mary Cardwell Dawson). (Box-folder 14/50)
    - Overstreet, Geraldine, undated (Box-folder 14/51)
    - Peeler, Lawrence, 1941, Mr. Peeler was the first Afro-American member of the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra. (Box-folder 14/52)
    - Pigskin Club of Washington, Inc. Twenty-sixth Annual Awards Dinner, Statler-Hilton Hotel, December 14, 1963, Oversize photo.; Walter M. Dawson was a member of this organization. (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Pigskin Club of Washington, Inc. Twenty-seventh Annual Awards Dinner, Statler-Hilton Hotel, December 12, 1964, Oversize photo.; Walter M. Dawson was a member of this organization. (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Powell, Aaron, undated (Box-folder 14/53)
    - Poyas, Dorothy, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 14/54)
    - Price, Sammy, 1944, Photograph is inscribed to "Willis" and is dated "3/1/44". (Box-folder 14/55)
    - Prince, Ulysses, undated (Box-folder 14/56)
    - Pryor, Vannye, undated (Box-folder 14/57)
    - Publicity photographs. Chicago Opera Guild activities and events, 1941 and undated, 15 photographs. (Box-folder 14/58)
    - Publicity photographs. New York Opera Guild activities and events, undated, 12 photographs. (Box-folder 14/59)
    - Publicity photographs. Pittsburgh Opera Guild activities and events, undated, Ten photographs. (Box-folder 14/60)
    - Publicity photographs. Washington, D.C. Opera Guild activities and events, 1951 and undated, 28 photographs. (Box-folder 14/61)
    - Publicity photographs. Unknown location, undated, 25 photographs. (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Quinn, Lorraine, undated (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Rahn, Muriel, 1949 and undated, Seven photographs (plus two photocopies) (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Rainbow, John, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Reed, Napoleon, undated (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Reese, Everett Watson, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Reid, Melbourne, undated (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Relatives of Mary Cardwell Dawson, undated, Five photographs. (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Rhea, La Julia, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Richardson, Mayme, undated (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Ricks, Jesse, undated (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Ringler, Jacque, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Robinson, Miss, undated, Miss Robinson was the daughter of Mary Nell Robinson. (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Rogers, Audrey, undated (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, undated, Photograph has been cut to remove someone from the image. (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Rubes, Jan, undated (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Saint James A.M.E. Church, undated (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Schuyler, Philippa Duke, undated, Inscribed to Mr. and Mrs. Dawson. (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Scott, Sirly, undated (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Shaw, Peggy Pierce, undated (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Sissle, Noble, late 1940s, Six photographs. (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Smith, Ethel Hardy, undated (Box-folder 15/22)
    - Smith, Jackson, undated (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Smith, Lillian Miller, undated (Box-folder 15/24)
    - Smith, Paul A., undated (Box-folder 15/25)
    - Social groups. Chicago, undated (Box-folder 15/26)
    - Social groups. Pittsburgh, undated, Five photographs. (Box-folder 15/27)
    - Social groups. Washington, D.C., undated, 19 photographs. (Box-folder 15/28)
    - Social groups. Unknown location, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/29)
    - The Southernaires (male vocal group), undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/30)
    - Stills, Vivian J., undated (Box-folder 15/31)
    - Stone, Theodore Charles, undated (Box-folder 15/32)
    - Stor, Jean, June 17, 1937, Inscribed and dated to Mary Cardwell Dawson. (Box-folder 15/33)
    - Taylor, Francena, undated, On reverse: Francena Taylor as "The Voice" in Ouanga. (Box-folder 15/34)
    - Tibbs, Roy, undated, Mr. Tibbs was Lillian Evanti's husband. (Box-folder 15/35)
    - La Traviata, 1944 and undated, 16 photographs; one negative. (Box-folder 15/36, 65/11)
    - Vajda, Frederick, 1943, Three photographs.; One photograph is inscribed to Mary Cardwell Dawson and is dated August 1, 1943, Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 15/37)
    - Vincent, Fritz, undated, On reverse: Fritz Vincent as La Bossal in Ouanga. (Box-folder 15/38)
    - Vincent and Reed (Dancers), undated (Box-folder 15/39)
    - Voorhees, Bettye, undated, Five photographs. (Box-folder 15/40, 65/3)
    - Vroman, Mary Elizabeth, undated (Box-folder 15/41)
    - Watson, Lawrence, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/42)
    - White, Clarence Cameron, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/43)
    - White, Leafie, undated (Box-folder 15/44)
    - Williams, Camilla, undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/45)
    - Williams, Virginia, undated (Box-folder 15/46)
    - Wilson, Horace, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/47)
  - Unidentified Individuals, Groups and Productions (Box 15, 65)
    - Unidentified groups, undated, Several photos found in Box 65/5 contain various city opera guild administrative boards and committees.; 38 photographs. (Box-folder 15/48, 65/4-5, 14)
    - Unidentified individuals (Chicago photographers), undated, Two photographs. (Box-folder 15/49)
    - Unidentified individuals (New York photographers), undated, Three photographs (one inscribed but unable to read). (Box-folder 15/50)
    - Unidentified individuals (Pittsburgh photographers), undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/51)
    - Unidentified individuals (Washington, D.C. photographers), undated, Six photographs. (Box-folder 15/52)
    - Unidentified individuals (Unknown location), undated, 22 photographs. (Box-folder 15/53)
    - Unidentified performances, undated, Three photographs. (Box-folder 15/54, 65/12)
- Programs and Promotional Materials, 1926-1997, (59 folders) (Box 1-6, 65-67)
  Includes programs, press releases, advertising, posters, draft copies of advertising and press releases, tickets, and newspaper reviews for concerts, musical performances, benefits, and other related events. The series is divided into two subseries: the first contains materials produced or sponsored by the National Negro Opera Company and its immediate predecessors, the National Negro Opera Foundation, and the various city-based National Negro Opera Company-affiliated opera guilds. In addition, it contains materials from concerts given by prominant stars of the National Negro Opera Company such as benefits and fundraising events for future operatic productions. The second subseries contains materials from concerts and events that are not directly related to the National Negro Opera Company, but which Mrs. Dawson attended. These document the African-American concert scene from the 1930s to the early 1960s.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Materials Related to the National Negro Opera Company and Other Affiliated Musical Ensembles, 1926-1997, undated (Box 1-4, 65-67)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1926-1934 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1941 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material. Poster: Aida performance, October 10, 1941, 1941 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, circa 1942, Draft "mock-up" promotional item for a proposed book to contain a projected one million names of individuals pledging support for the creation of a National Negro Opera Company and Symphony Orchestra. (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1942 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1943 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1944 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1945 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1946 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1947 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1948 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1949 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1950 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1951 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1952 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1953 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1954 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1955 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1956 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material. Poster: Ouanga performance, Metropolitan Opera House, New York, May 27, 1956 (Box 67)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1957 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material. Poster: The Ordering of Moses performance, Hillhouse High School, New Haven, Conn., May 5, 1957 (Box 67)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1958 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1959 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1960 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1961 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1962 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1965 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Programs/Promotional Material (oversize), 1933-1963 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material (oversize). Publicity drafts, 1940s-1950s (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material - Printed Profiles, undated (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Programs/Promotional Material - Typed Profiles, undated (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material - Press Releases, undated (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material - Solicitation Letters, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Non-National Negro Opera Company Materials, 1934-1987, undated (Box 4-6, 66)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1934-1941 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1943, 1950s (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1944 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1945 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1946 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1947 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1948 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1949 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1950 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1951 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1952 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1953 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1954 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1955 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1956 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1957 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1958 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1959 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1960 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1961 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1962 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, 1963-1987 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Programs/Promotional Material, undated (Box-folder 6/5-7)